# Rayhan Shidqi



#### **Personal Information**

# Project Portfolio: rayhanshidqi.com

#### Email:

rayhanshidqi.j@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/rayhanshidqi

#### GitHub:

github.com/eaqyyy

#### **Education**

#### **BINUS University**

Bachelor of Computer Science 2017 – February 2021 (expected) GPA 3.5 / 4.0

#### Summary

Rayhan is a final year computer science student that is expected to graduate in February 2021. He will be graduating from university within 3.5 years with 1 year worth of internship experience. He is well-versed in many programming languages and specialized in full-stack development. To hone his teamwork and public speaking skills, Rayhan also has won a few international debating tournaments.

#### **Technical Skills**

Programming

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Python
- Java
- C/C++

Framework & Database

- React
- Angular
- Express
- Django
- NoSQL & SQL

## **Experience**

Full-stack Developer Intern — February 2020 to February 2021 Jenius (Bank BTPN), Jakarta

- Developed an applicant tracking software to ease and speed-up recruitment process of IT talent.
- Developed a server notification software that automatically deliver report analysis & critical server alerts.
- Stack used: React/Angular, Express, and MongoDB.
- The code are written in a clean and testable manner.

**Technical Support Intern** – January 2016 to March 2016 **LKBN Antara, High School Summer Break Internship**, Jakarta

- Designed networking route for different office floors.
- Virtualized server with Microsoft HyperV.

### **Academic Achievements**

- Recepient of Outstanding Students Scholarship, 2019
- Australasians Intervarsity Debating Championship, 2019 EFL Champion. The biggest intercontinental debating tournament ever held. Topics of discussion includes technology, economy, politics, and environment.
- United Asians Debating Championship, 2019 –
  EFL Champion & Top 10 Best EFL Speaker Nominee.
  A highly-celebrated debating tournament that welcomes prestigious universities across Asia.
- Asian English Olympics, 2020 –
  Debating Champion & 4th Best Speaker. Matched against students from multiple countries in Asia; China, Hong Kong, Taiwan, Bangladesh, and Vietnam.